Guide to the John Burroughs Papers, 1850-1991 (bulk 1860-1921)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES IX. PHOTOGRAPHS, 1857-1927
  - Slabsides
    - JB sitting on porch steps — Copy from album of Helen Clemence St. Peter (VC 1907), circa 1907 (Folder 58.58)
    - JB sitting on porch steps — Copy from album of Jeannette H. Ware (VC 1905), undated (Folder 58.59)
    - JB sitting on porch steps with Anne Bowden (VC 1918) behind him — removed from album of an unidentified VC student, Fall 1908 (Folder 58.60)
    - JB sitting on porch steps — Photographer: Hildegarde Kneeland (VC 1911), undated (Folder 58.61)
    - JB sitting on porch steps with his dog Rover II, circa 1907 (Folder 58.62)
    - JB sitting on porch steps — Photographer: Herbert E. Mills (VC Economics Dept.), circa 1914 (Folder 58.63)
    - JB sitting on porch steps — Photographer: Herbert E. Mills (VC Economics Dept.), circa 1914 (Folder 58.64)
    - JB standing at base of porch steps, circa 1911 (Folder 58.65)
    - JB standing at base of porch steps — removed from album of unidentified VC student, circa 1908 (Folder 58.66)
    - JB sitting on porch, undated (Folder 58.67)
    - JB sitting on porch with dog — Photographer: Herbert E. Mills (VC Economics Dept.)?, undated (Folder 58.68)
    - JB sitting outside cabin — Copy from album of Elizabeth Emerson Benedict (VC 1920), 1918 (Folder 58.69)
    - JB standing outside cabin, undated (Folder 58.70)
    - JB sitting with back against cabin wall — from album of VC Class of 1914, undated (Folder 58.71)
    - JB standing in field outside cabin, 1901 (Folder 58.72)
    - JB sawing wood outside the cabin, undated (Folder 58.73)
    - JB sitting on rocks near the cabin, undated (Folder 58.74)
    - JB sitting on rocks near the cabin — Photographer: "A.L.W" (VC 1906), circa 1906 (Folder 58.75)
    - JB sitting on rocks near the cabin — Photographer: "A.L.W" (VC 1906) — Copy from album of Helen Clemence St. Peter (VC 1907), circa 1906 (Folder 58.76)
    - JB sitting on "Julian's rock" above the cabin, undated (Folder 58.77)
  - Riverby
    - Bark Study exterior, undated (Folder 60.15)
    - Bark Study exterior, circa 1894 (Folder 58.78)
    - JB in front of the Bark Study — Photographer: Walsh, undated (Folder 64.4)
    - JB seated in the Bark Study — Photographer: Clyde Fisher, 6 Nov 1915 (Folder 58.79)
    - JB collecting sap, undated (Folder 58.80)
    - JB building a birdhouse, stone house in background, undated (Folder 58.81)
  - Roxbury
    - Two women and a man (possibly JB) in the fields of "the old homestead,", undated (Folder 58.82)
    - JB bringing in the cows on the farm — Photographer: Julian Burroughs, undated (Folder 58.83)
    - Cows in the fields with "Old Clump" in the background, undated (Folder 58.84)
    - Winter scene including a sled in front of the 1850 farmhouse, undated (Folder 58.85)
    - Rear view of "the milk house...the wood shed...and the old elm,", undated (Folder 58.86)
    - JB in front of Woodchuck Lodge — Copy of postcard, undated (Folder 58.87)
    - JB in front of Woodchuck Lodge, undated (Folder 58.88)
    - JB seated on "the giant stairs" near Woodchuck Lodge — Photographer: Clyde Fisher, 29 Sep 1918 (Folder 58.89)
  - Burroughs and Vassar College
    - JB with students at the summer house at Riverby, 1894 (Folder 60.13)
    - JB with students at the summer house at Riverby — Found in Elizabeth H. Haight's copy of Wake-Robin, 1894 (Folder 58.90)
    - Henry Van Ingen and five members of VC 1894 on the road to Slabsides: Ellen Chater, Leonora Howe?, Henry Van Ingen, Elizabeth H. Haight, Lila Patterson, Katherine Spiers, and Ethel Moore (Folder 58.91)
    - JB with Winifred Ball on Slabsides porch steps, 1896 or 1897 (Folder 58.134)
    - JB with Henry Van Ingen on Slabsides porch steps, 1896 or 1897 (Folder 58.135)
    - JB inside Slabsides with students including "Augusta," Mabel Patterson (VC 1899), Phebe Beadle (VC 1900), "Bent," and "Blanche,", circa 1899 (Folder 58.92)
    - JB picnicking with Vassar and Cornell students and faculty on top of Mt. Seward after a hike from Camp Ampusand, 1900 (Folder 58.93)
    - JB with Vassar and Cornell people at Camp Ampusand, 1900 (Folder 58.94)
    - JB with Adelaide Crapsey {VC 1901) outside Slabsides (Folder 58.136)
    - JB with students on the porch steps at Slabsides — including Clare Allen (VC 1903), Elisabeth Allen (VC 1904), Constance Warren (VC 1904), Helen Kohlsaat (VC 1904), Helen Wood (VC 1904), Annie Wood (VC 1904) and others — Print from Glass Negative, May 1904 (Folder 58.95)
    - JB with students on the porch steps at Slabsides — including Clare Allen (VC 1903), Elisabeth Allen (VC 1904), Constance Warren (VC 1904), Helen Kohlsaat (VC 1904), Helen Wood (VC 1904), Annie Wood (VC 1904) and others — Copy from album of Ruth Crippen (VC 1904), May 1904 (Folder 58.96)
    - JB with students on the porch steps at Slabsides — including Clare Allen (VC 1903), Elisabeth Allen (VC 1904), Constance Warren (VC 1904), Helen Kohlsaat (VC 1904), Helen Wood (VC 1904), Annie Wood (VC 1904) and others — Copy from album of Jeanette H. Ware (VC 1905), May 1904 (Folder 58.97)
    - Students walking in the woods, presumably near Slabsides — Copy from album of Jeanette H. Ware (VC 1905), circa 1904 (Folder 58.98)
    - JB with four members of VC 1905 on the porch steps at Slabsides: Claire Reiley?, Harriet Manning, Mary Reed, and Marie Pinckard (Folder 58.99)
    - JB with teachers on the way to Slabsides, including Elizabeth H. Haight, 11 March 1906? (Folder 58.100)
    - JB with Margaret Floy Washburn — Copy from album of Margaret L. Warner (VC 1910), circa 1906-1910 (Folder 58.137)
    - JB with students and faculty on the porch steps at Slabsides — Copy from album of Helen Lathrop Thompson (VC 1911), 28 Oct 1907 (Folder 58.101)
    - JB walking down road to Slabsides with students — Copy from album of Helen Clemence St. Peter (VC 1907), circa 1907 (Folder 58.102)
    - JB with students sitting on rocks in front of Slabsides — Copy from album of Helen Clemence St. Peter (VC 1907), circa 1907 (Folder 58.103)
    - JB with students picnicking on a hill — Copy from album of Helen Clemence St. Peter (VC 1907), circa 1907 (Folder 58.104)
    - JB with students picnicking on a hill — Copy from album of Helen Clemence St. Peter (VC 1907), circa 1907 (Folder 58.105)
    - JB speaking with students outside, 17 Oct 1908 (Folder 58.120)
    - JB speaking to students outside, 17 Oct 1908? (Folder 58.132)
    - JB with students outside Slabsides in winter, circa 1908 (Folder 58.106)
    - JB with students outside Slabsides in winter, circa 1908 (Folder 58.107)
    - JB sitting in the woods with Vassar people including Elizabeth H. Haight (VC 1894) — Copy from Haight's album, Aug 1909 (Folder 58.108)
    - JB sitting in the woods with Vassar people including Elizabeth H. Haight (VC 1894) — Copy from an alumnae album, Aug 1909 (Folder 58.109)
    - JB picnicking under a tree at Stony Creek with Vassar people including, Helen Haight, Elizabeth H. Haight, their mother, Florence Gilman, Paul Swan, and others, 1909 (Folder 58.110)
    - JB sitting on porch at Stony Creek, where he visited with Vassar faculty, 1909 (Folder 58.130)
    - JB sitting on a hammock at Stony Creek, where he visited with Vassar faculty, 1909 (Folder 58.131)
    - JB with faculty outside Slabsides, 21 May 1910 (Folder 58.111)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch behind him — Copy from an alumnae album, 1909? (Folder 58.112)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch steps behind him — Copy from an alumnae album, 1913 (Folder 58.113)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch steps behind him — Copy from an alumnae album, 1913 (Folder 58.114)
    - JB with students in front of Slabsides — Photographer: Elizabeth Wright (VC 1916), 1914 (Folder 58.115)
    - JB on Slabsides porch with Mary Mills, Harold Mills, and unidentified woman — Photographer: Herbert E. Mills (VC Economics Dept.), circa 1914 (Folder 58.116)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch steps — Copy from VC Class of 1914 album, circa 1914 (Folder 58.117)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch steps behind him — Copy from album of Georgina R. Stone (VC 1914), circa 1914 (Folder 58.118)
    - JB with Margaret F. Washburn on Slabsides porch behind him — Copy from album of Georgina R. Stone (VC 1914), circa 1914 (Folder 58.133)
    - JB with students on rocks near Slabsides, 1917 (Folder 58.119)
    - JB at Founder's Day baseball game, 1919 (Folder 60.10)
    - JB at Founder's Day baseball game, 1919; [mounted] (Folder 60.11)
    - JB at Founder's Day baseball game, 1919; [enlarged and zoomed] (Folder 60.12)
    - JB at Founder's Day baseball game — Copy from album of Phebe Poole Baxter (VC 1921), 1919 (Folder 58.121)
    - JB and students at Slabsides, circa 1920 (Folder 58.122)
    - JB and students walking near Slabsides, circa 1920 (Folder 58.123)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch steps — Copy 1, undated (Folder 58.124)
    - JB with students on Slabsides porch steps — Copy 2, undated (Folder 58.125)
    - Students on Slabsides porch steps, undated (Folder 58.126)
    - JB outside in a field, surrounded by students, undated (Folder 58.127)
    - Henry Noble MacCracken on the Slabsides porch steps, undated (Folder 58.128)
    - JB talking to Marjorie and Henry Noble MacCracken near Slabsides, undated (Folder 58.129)
    - JB, barely visible under an umbrella, with Vassar students, undated (Folder 59.93)
    - Photocopies of Burroughs images in Vassar College student albums (Folder 63.63)
  - Burroughs with Family
    - JB and Julian Burroughs with a car given by Henry Ford, circa 1914 (Folder 58.138)
    - JB holding Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley, circa 1904 (Folder 58.139)
    - JB reading to granddaughters Elizabeth and Ursula — Photographer: Laura MacKay, undated (Folder 58.140)
    - JB reading to granddaughters Elizabeth and Ursula — Photographer: Laura MacKay, undated (Folder 58.141)
    - JB with grandson John Burroughs sitting in car given by Henry Ford, circa 1914 (Folder 58.142)
    - JB with grandchildren Elizabeth, Ursula and John on "Boyhood Rock,", undated (Folder 58.143)
    - JB at Wisteria Cottage, La Jolla, CA, with granddaughter Ursula, Clara Barrus, and the Barrus nieces, undated (Folder 58.144)
    - JB and his brother inside slabsides, undated (Folder 58.145)
    - JB and family on the Wawee on the Hudson, undated (Folder 58.146)
    - JB, Emily Burroughs, Granddaughter Ursula, Ethel Van Benschoten and Orlando Rouland on the Wawee on the Hudson, undated (Folder 58.147)
    - JB and family with a car in front of house in Roxbury?, undated (Folder 58.148)
    - JB with Laura MacKay at Roxbury, 1913 (Folder 58.149)
    - JB with Ursula, Clara Barrus, and other Barrus family at Lake Mohonk, 1904 (Folder 60.2)
  - Burroughs with Friends
    - JB with Bertrude Ballard at Squirrel Island, ME, 1918 (Folder 58.150)
    - JB with Clara Barrus in a field, undated (Folder 58.151)
    - JB with Clara Barrus on a bench, undated (Folder 58.152)
    - JB with Poultney Bigelow, undated (Folder 58.153)
    - JB with Luther Burbank, Edith Simonds, and Henry F. Finch in Santa Rosa, CA, 16 June 1909 (Folder 58.154)
    - JB with Luther Burbank, Mr. and Mrs. Hart and Mrs. Finch in Santa Rosa, CA, 16 June 1909 (Folder 58.155)
    - JB with Thomas Edison, Harvey Firestone, Harvey Firestone, Jr., Henry Ford and Fred Seeley in front of the Grove Park Inn, Asheville, NC, undated; [image slightly torn] (Folder 58.156)
    - JB with Thomas Edison and Henry Ford, Fort Meyers, FL, 1914; [postcard] (Folder 59.27)
    - JB with Thomas Edison, Harvey Firestone, Henry Ford, Edward N. Hurly, and unidentified man, undated (Folder 59.28)
    - JB with Henry Ford in the original Ford automobile in Dearborn, 1913 (Folder 58.157)
    - JB with Henry Ford in Ford's Office, 1913? (Folder 58.158)
    - JB with Henry Ford and Frank Sanborn at Walden Pond — Photographer: Glen Buck, 31 Aug 1913 (Folder 58.159)
    - JB with Henry Ford and Frank Sanborn at Walden Pond, 31 Aug 1913 (Folder 59.62)
    - JB with Henry Ford, Frank Sanborn and Mrs. Buck in the Emerson Garden, Concord, MA — Photographer: Glen Buck, 31 Aug 1913 (Folder 59.64)
    - JB with Hamlin Garland at Woodchuck Lodge— Photographer: George Stone, 20 July 1919 (Folder 58.160)
    - JB with Hamlin Garland, Clara Barrus and Others at Yama Farms, 2 Apr 1920 (Folder 58.161)
    - JB chopping wood at Yama Farms on his 83rd birthday, 3 Apr 1920 (Folder 58.162)
    - JB with William Keith on Mt. Tamalpais, CA, 28 Apr 1909 (Folder 58.163)
    - JB with "Mr. Lu," 71 Elm Street, Oneonta, Aug 1902 (Folder 59.24)
    - JB with John Muir at the Grand Canyon, 1909 (Folder 58.164)
    - JB standing with John Muir near Pasadena, CA, 1909 (Folder 58.165)
    - JB sitting with John Muir near Pasadena, CA, 1909 (Folder 58.166)
    - JB posing for Pietro at Woodchuck Lodge, undated (Folder 59.1)
    - JB posing for Pietro at Woodchuck Lodge, undated (Folder 59.2)
    - JB posing for Pietro at Woodchuck Lodge, undated (Folder 59.3)
    - JB with Edith and Theodore Roosevelt on Slabsides porch — Photographer: Julian Burroughs, 10 July 1903 (Folder 59.4)
    - JB with Theodore Roosevelt and others at Fort Yellowstone — copy of Underwood and Underwood stereograph?, 1903 (Folder 59.5)
    - JB with Orlando and Minnie Rouland on Slabsides porch with dog, undated (Folder 59.6)
    - JB with Orlando and Minnie Rouland, undated (Folder 60.9)
    - JB with Mr. and Mrs. Frank Seaman of Yama Farms, undated (Folder 59.7)
    - JB with Helen Gould Sheppard and the Gould Family and friends at Roxbury, undated (Folder 59.8)
    - JB with Helen Gould Sheppard and the Gould Family and friends at Roxbury, undated (Folder 59.9)
    - JB with Helen Gould Sheppard and the Gould Family and friends at Roxbury, undated (Folder 59.10)
    - JB with Helen Gould Sheppard and the Gould Family and friends at Roxbury, undated (Folder 59.11)
    - JB with Helen Gould Sheppard and the Gould Family and friends at Roxbury, undated (Folder 59.12)
    - JB with sons of Helen Gould Sheppard at Roxbury, 1915 (Folder 59.13)
    - JB with others at a pageant on Helen Gould Sheppard's farm at Roxbury, 1915 (Folder 59.14)
    - JB with others at a pageant on Helen Gould Sheppard's farm at Roxbury, 1915 (Folder 59.15)
    - Pageant on Helen Gould Sheppard's farm at Roxbury, 1915 (Folder 59.16)
    - JB with Ida Tarbox, Julian Burroughs and others, undated (Folder 59.17)
    - JB with "Mrs. Knox Taylor" (Sarah K. Taylor?) — with note on back from JB, 27 March 1907 (Folder 59.18)
    - JB with the Van Benschotens and Lyalls outside Slabsides, 15 May 1905 (Folder 59.19)
    - JB with unidentified people in swimsuits — photo of a another photo, undated (Folder 59.20)
    - JB with unidentified child on Slabsides steps, undated (Folder 59.21)
    - JB with unidentified man at Lake View Point, Cascade Park, 24 May 1910 (Folder 59.22)
    - JB with unidentified woman on Slabsides steps, undated (Folder 59.23)
    - JB with unidentified child at Roxmor Inn, Woodland Valley, 1907 (Folder 59.25)
  - Friends and Family (not including Burroughs)
    - Barrus, Clara — in "The Nest" at Riverby, June 1921 (Folder 59.29)
    - Barrus, Clara — Portrait, undated (Folder 59.30)
    - Beal, Mary — Portraits and snapshots, 1909-1927, undated (Folders 59.31-46)
    - Beal, Mary — Photos of California, mostly the Mojave, circa1909-1950 (Folder 59.47-48)
    - Beal, Mary — Photos of the Paiute, undated (Folder 59.49)
    - Burroughs, Emily — with her three children at Woodchuck Lodge, undated (Folder 59.50)
    - Burroughs, Julian — Photographer: Beth Elinor Fisher, 25 Apr 1926 (Folder 59.51)
    - Burroughs, Julian — in his boat on the Shataca — Photographer: Julian Burroughs, undated (Folder 60.14)
    - Burroughs, Ursula — holding Elizabeth Burroughs Kelley, circa 1904 (Folder 59.52)
    - Burroughs, Ursula?, undated (Folder 59.53)
    - Burroughs Family, miscellaneous and unidentified, 1921, undated (Folder 59.102)
    - Carmen, Bliss — from Laura MacKay's Carmen material, undated (Folder 59.54)
    - Connell, Mrs. Karl — Photographer: John Burroughs, circa 1916 (Folder 59.55)
    - Darwin, Charles — Purchased by JB in London, 1881 (Folder 59.56)
    - Edison, Thomas — with Mina Edison at West Park, possibly for JB's funeral, undated (Folder 59.57)
    - Emerson and Hawthorne — Graves and the Old Manse — EBK's snapshots (Folder 59.58)
    - North, Amanda — with unidentified girl, undated (Folder 59.59)
    - Rickert, Edith — Copy of photo she presented to JB in 1906 (Folder 59.60)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore — Possibly at Yosemite, undated (Folder 59.61)
    - Sanderson, Gertrude, undated (Folder 60.16)
    - Thoreau, Henry David — Bust by Walton Ricketson, inscribed to JB by the artist, undated (Folder 59.65)
    - Thoreau, Henry David — Artifacts and home interiors — EBK's snapshots (Folder 59.66)
    - Thoreau, Henry David — Grave and home exteriors — EBK's snapshots (Folder 59.67)
    - Thoreau, Henry David — Walden Pond and Concord River — EBK's snapshots (Folder 59.68)
    - Traubel, Anne — with her children Gertrude and Wallace, July 1894 (Folder 59.69)
    - Whitman, Walt — Tintype copy of 1842 daguerreotype, circa 1870 (Folder 59.70)
    - Whitman, Walt — snapshot of the 1842 tintype and information about it from EBK and William Culp Darrah (Folder 59.71)
    - Whitman, Walt — Smaller version of portrait that hung in Slabsides (Folder 59.72)
    - Whitman, Walt — Birthplace — EBK's snapshots (Folder 59.73)
    - Whitman, Walt — damaged "when Slabsides was sprayed,", undated (Folder 60.17)
    - Whitman, Walt — Photographer: Sophie Williams, 1886 (Folder 60.18)
    - Whitman, Walt — Photographer: George Gardner Rockwood (Folder 60.21)
    - Whitman, Walt — with cardboard butterfly, [copy of circa 1873 image at Library of Congress] (Folder 59.96)
    - Whitman, Walt — grave site (Folder 59.97)
    - Wiley, Farida — Holding a chick, undated (Folder 59.74)
    - Wiley, Farida — At JB's grave with others, undated (Folder 59.75)
  - Schools
    - Roxbury, NY — attended — EBK's snapshot (Folder 59.76)
    - Harpersfield, NY — Wanted to attend — JB seated on steps (Folder 59.77)
    - Harpersfield, NY — Wanted to attend — JB standing in front (Folder 59.78)
    - Harpersfield, NY — Wanted to attend — JB walking up road (Folder 59.79)
    - Hedding Literary Institute, Ashland Seminary, NY — attended 1854-1855 — copy of sketch (Folder 59.80)
    - Tongore, NY — Taught at, 1854-1855 — sent to JB by Mrs. Cragin, 1900 (Folder 59.87)
    - Tongore, NY — Taught at, 1854-1855 — copy of exterior shot, circa 1900 (Folder 59.88)
    - Polo, IL — Taught at, 1856-1857 — 3 photos of the town (Folder 59.81)
    - Highland Falls, NY — Taught at, 1857 — 3 EBK snapshots (Folder 59.82)
    - Highland Falls, NY — Taught at, 1857 — copy of school house photo illustration (Folder 59.83)
    - Rosendale, NY — Taught at, 1858 — EBK's snapshot (Folder 59.84)
    - Marlboro, NY — Taught at, 1861 — 4 EBK snapshots (Folder 59.85)
    - West Point Military Academy, NY — Used the library of, 1863 (Folder 59.86)
  - Miscellaneous
    - The Harriman Expedition, 1899 (Folder 59.89)
    - Sculpture of Burroughs in Toledo, OH (Folder 59.90)
    - Portrait by Princess Lwoff-Parlaghy (Folder 64.3)
    - Falls on Black Creek, near Slabsides (Folder 59.91)
    - Illustration of U.S. Treasury Building, Washington, D.C., circa 1865 (Folder 59.92)
    - Illustration of the Capitol building, Washington, D.C., circa 1865 (Folder 59.100)
    - Burroughs home in Washington, D.C — EBK's snapshots (Folder 59.101)
    - Interior of Minnie Rouland's home in Twilight Park, NY (Folder 59.94)
    - Rouland portrait of JB (Folder 59.95)
    - Mohonk Mountain House — Photographer: John Burroughs, 1904? (Folder 60.4)
    - Album of Charles Lumis cyanotypes, sent to Clara Barrus by Lumis in 1922 (Folder 60.1)
    - Album of snapshots of a camping trip to Ampersand Creek in the Adirondacks, Aug 1900 (Box 60)
- Series X. G. CLYDE FISHER PAPERS, 1902-1927
  - Ephemera
    - Ticket to lectures by G. Clyde Fisher at Columbia University, 1927 (Folder 67.1)
  - Letters
    - Barrus, Clara to G. Clyde Fisher, 1920 Nov-Dec; (3 letters) (Folder 67.2)
    - Burroughs, Emily to G. Clyde Fisher, 1919 Dec 17; (1 letter) (Folder 67.3)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, 1902 Jul 7; (1 letter) (Folder 67.4)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, [1913?] Nov 12; (1 letter) (Folder 67.4)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, [1916] Mar 9; (1 letter) (Folder 67.5)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, [1918] Oct 28; (1 letter) (Folder 67.5)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, 1919 Jan 1; (1 letter) (Folder 67.6)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, 1919 Jul 17; (1 letter, 1 enclosure) (Folder 67.6)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, 1920 Dec 20; (1 letter) (Folder 67.7)
    - Burroughs, John to G. Clyde Fisher, 1920 Nov 19; (1 letter) (Folder 67.7)
    - Fisher, G. Clyde to John Burroughs - draft, 1916 Jun 25; (6 p.) (Folder 67.8)
    - Fisher, G. Clyde to John Burroughs - draft, 1916 Jul 8; (4 p.) (Folder 67.9)
    - Fisher, G. Clyde to John Burroughs - draft, 1920 Dec 7; (12 p.) (Folder 67.10)
    - Envelopes (empty), undated; (2 envelopes) (Folder 67.11)
  - Photographs
    - JB and a record Hubbard Squash - Photographer: G. Clyde Fisher, 1918 Sep 29; (4x5 in, mounted) (Folder 67.12)
    - JB and Clara Barrus on the porch at Woodchuck Lodge, NY - Photographer: G. Clyde Fisher, 1919 Aug 18; (4x5 in, mounted) (Folder 67.12)
    - JB and G. Clyde Fisher examining an herb near Slabsides, NY, 1920 Nov 7; (4x5 in) (Folder 67.13)
    - JB and John Muir sitting in Yosemite - Photographer: F.P. Clatworthy, 1909 May; (10x14 in) (Box 68)
    - JB and John Muir walking in Yosemite - Photographer: F.P. Clatworthy, 1909 May; (8x14 in) (Box 68)
    - JB and Ruth Anna Fisher at Slabsides, NY - Photographer: G. Clyde Fisher, 1917 May 26; (4x5 in) (Folder 67.14)
    - JB on the porch at Woodchuck Lodge, NY - Photographer: G. Clyde Fisher, 1918 Sep 29; (4x5 in) (Folder 67.15)
    - JB with Henry Ford, Harvey Firestone, Frank Seaman, and Thomas Edison at Yama Farms, Napanoch, NY, [1914?]; (6x8 in) (Folder 67.16)
    - JB with Henry Ford, Poultney Bigelow, and others, 1914; (4x5 in) (Folder 67.16)
    - "Uncle" Pink Ward "fiddling" for earth worms near Red Bay, Florida - Photographer: G. Clyde Fisher, 1915 Aug 4; (4x5 in) (Folder 67.17)
    - "Uncle" Pink Ward with three bear skins and some furs, Florida - Photographer: G. Clyde Fisher, 1916 Dec 31; (4x5 in) (Folder 67.17)
    - Unidentified (likely related to one of JB's outings with Henry Ford), undated; (4x6 in) (Folder 67.16)
  - Writings
    - Burroughs, John, "Fuss & Feathers," draft, annotated by G. Clyde Fisher, undated; (TS, 5 p.) (Folder 67.18)
    - Burroughs, John, "The Eternal Feminine," draft, corrected, [1915 Oct?]; (TS, 1 p.) (Folder 67.19)
    - Fisher, G. Clyde, introduction to a collection of JB's writings, draft, undated; (MS, 6 p.) (Folder 67.20)
    - Fisher, G. Clyde, untitled writing about birds, draft, undated; (MS, 12 p.) (Folder 67.21)
    - Fisher, G. Clyde, untitled writings about JB, drafts, undated; (TS, 2 p.) (Folder 67.22)